{
    "id": "a69fabac991049f9b0c37ccdf80ad97f",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is both clever ……………………… industrious.",
            "description": "The correct conjunction is both...and...",
            "answers": [
                "as well as",
                "and",
                "also"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………. his disability, he has never failed at anything.",
            "description": "Despite is a preposition expressing contrast. ",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "Despite",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She has her shortcomings …………………………, I can’t help liking her.",
            "description": "However is used to introduce a contrasting idea. ",
            "answers": [
                "however",
                "although",
                "despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You should wait here ……………………….. I return.",
            "description": "Either until or till is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "till",
                "up to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. you take these tablets, you won’t get well.",
            "description": "Unless means if not. If you do not take these tablets, you won't get well. ",
            "answers": [
                "Unless",
                "If",
                "Without"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Something must have fallen ………………………. I heard a thud.",
            "description": "For is possible here in a formal style. Because is also correct. ",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "because",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. he is not educated, he is very intelligent.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "As",
                "Even as"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. it was already late, we called it a day.",
            "description": "As gives the reason. ",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "If",
                "While"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. you are free tomorrow, we can go for a drive.",
            "description": "If expresses a condition. ",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Whether",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I received the letter two days ……………………..",
            "description": "Ago is used to count back from a present moment.",
            "answers": [
                "ago",
                "before",
                "past"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the house …………………………. he was born.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "there",
                "here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It has been months ………………………. I heard anything from her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}